MAULANA MALIK IBRAHIM

+6283857671574 | Banyuwangi, Indonesia | mallexibra@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/mallexibra/

SUMMARY

I am Maulana Malik Ibrahim, a Fullstack Web Developer with more than 1 year of experience working on freelance projects successfully. One of my skills in creative web development is Next.js and Laravel. Has led projects, both graphic design projects and website development and managed time efficiently. My leadership skills are strengthened by experience as Chair in several organizations. I am confident I can make a positive contribution, combining technical and leadership skills, to your team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Freelancer

2022 - Present

- Working on a full stack website project.
- Working on a logo design project.
- Working on packaging/packaging label design projects.
- Doing video editing.

Finishing, Variant Printing & Offset (Internship)

Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

- Help with photo editing using Photoshop software
- · Assist in plate cutting
- Helping Finishing Banners
- Helping Finishing Notes, Calendars, Folders

EDUCATION

D4 TRPL, Banyuwangi State Polytechnic

Aug 2022 - Present

Semester 1 GPA: 3.60/4.00Semester 2 GPA: 3.83/4.00

TKJ, Kalibaru State Vocational School

Jul 2019 - Apr 2022

• Average score: 87.00

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Member, Entrepreneurship UKM

Periode 2022/2023

 Participate as a committee in the implementation of several Work Programs owned by Entrepreneurship UKM.

Chairman, MPK Kalibaru State Vocational School

2020/2021 Period

- Lead class meetings and deliberations to discuss important issues and find solutions together.
- Supervise the performance of the Kalibaru State Vocational School OSIS administrators for the 2021/2022 period.

Chairman, Kalibaru State Vocational School OSIS

2019/2020 Period

- Leading OSIS meetings and providing direction to members.
- Manage and guide OSIS members in carrying out their duties.
- Become a representative at meetings with OSIS throughout Banyuwangi district.

AWARDS AND VOLUNTEERING

• Lecturer Service in Pendarungan Village

2023

Helping create a website for monitoring Pendarungan village activities.

• 1st Place in Business Plan Competition

2023

Main winner of the 2023 Digital Office Management Summer Program Business Plan Competition at Airlanga University.

• Best Teamwork KMIPN V PENS Surabaya

2023

Won the Best Teamwork award in the ICT Business competition at KMIPN V PENS Surabaya.

• 2nd Place in Logo Design Competition

2023

Won 2nd Place in the 8th Anniversary Logo Design Competition of the Banyuwangi State Polytechnic Bidikmisi Communication Forum.

PROJECT

• Aplikasi Monitoring Kegiatan Desa Pendarungan

The Web-based Pendarungan Village Activity Monitoring Application is a platform used to manage data on Pendarungan Village Government activities.

PUTI Online

The PUTI Online application is a web-based application that can be used by students of the Informatics Engineering Department at the Banyuwangi State Polytechnic to report problems in the department so that the department can monitor student complaints easily.

• CAFESTUFF

The CAFESTUFF application is a web-based application used for renting cafeshop items.

SKILLS

Soft Skills

- Time management skills
- Organizational abilities
- Communication skills
- Ability to build relationships
- Project management capabilities

Hard Skill

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, Laravel, ReactJS, NextJS, Prisma, ExpressJS.
- Tools: Figma, Inkscape, Kdenlive, Notion, Trello, Git dan Github.
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL.